만나기로한 정보원일꺼야
Must be our guy.
그가 원하는게 뭘거같아?
What do you think he wants?
그는 좋은 사마리안이
될수없는건가?
What, he can't just be
a good Samaritan?
NSA요원이 실종된
가능성이 있어.
Tip about a possible
missing NSA agent
그나마 좋은 소식은
그가 착할수도 있다는거?
out of the goodness
of his heart?
켄자스에 있을수도 있겠는데.
Maybe in Kansas.
접선장소가 스타벅스같은
곳이면 좋잔아
Never want to meet at
a Starbucks, do they?
그쪽에서 원치않았어
No, they don't.
NCIS.
정보가 있다고요?
You have some
information for us?
함정이야!
It's a set-up.
♪ ♪
솵 솵
솵 NCIS: LA 6x15 솵
Forest for the Trees
Original Air Date on February 9, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ ♪
솵 솵
오마이갓
Oh, my God.
너무 맛있다
This is so good.
환상적인 맛을 가졌다고
자랑하던
Uh, what's the name
of the food truck
푸드트럭 이름이 뭐였어?
that you're having
this religious experience with?
건강에 좋은 음식
Life On Wheels.
Wholesome Food
for Life On Wheels.
진짜 솔직하게 얘기해서
And I-I got to be
completely honest with you.
이 음식으로 깨끗해진 기분이야
인생이 바꼈어
I feel like eating clean
has changed my life.
뭔소린지 알지?
You know what I mean?
나는 건강해졌고, 기분좋아졌고
힘도 넘쳐,
I'm healthier, I feel better,
I got more energy,
집중력이 강해진건 말할것도 없고
my focus is stronger--
이건.. 마치 기적이야
it's-it's like a...
it's like a miracle.
농담이지?
It's a joke is what it is.
기껏얘기해줬더니
And there it is on cue.
나를 부정적으로 만들려고하네
"고맙다"
Negative Nelly makes
an appearance. Thanks for that.
부정적으로 만든다고?
Negative Nelly?
나는 그냥.. 니가 뭐하는지
이해를 못하겠어
I just... I don't
understand why you do that.
뭘?
Do what?
맨날 내가 뭔갈 찾고
경험을 얘기하고
Every time I find something
I'm excited about,
그게 얼마나 나한테 이로운지
열정적으로 얘기를 하면
that I'm passionate about,
that's good for me,
너는 분위기를 깨버려
you just got to go,
and you got to tear it down.
나는 그런뜻이 아니..
No, I'm just
saying that because...
이번꺼는 진짜로 건강식에다가
And this place is
the healthiest.
신선하고 천연재료에..
It's-it's fresh,
and it's certified organic,
그리고 이건 농장에서
만드는걸꺼야
and it's sustainably-farmed,
and it's...
냉동
Frozen.
미안한데 뭐라고?
I'm sorry. What did you say?
그거 냉동식품인데
It's frozen.
트럭주인이 냉동식품을 사는걸 봤어
I saw them load the truck
at Smart and Final.
그럴리가..
/맞음
No way.
Way.
켄지 블라이 장담하냐
Kensi Blye guarantee.
켄지 블라이가 장담합니다.
젠장!
Damn it!
저 사기꾼들!!
Those con men.
저 비열한 거짓말장이들!!
Those conniving, lying...
18달러나 줬다고!!
I paid $18 for this.
너는 어떻게 맨날 낚이냐
미스터 유리온실씨
I'm not sure I'd be throwing
stones, Mr. Glass Greenhouse.
그건 또 뭔소리야
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
가정식 이탈리아 식사한적 있잔아
That home-cooked Italian meal
저번주에 니가 만들어줬던,
you made me last week?
기억나지? 너도알거야
Remember that?
You know, the one
니가 꼼꼼하게 확인하며
you made sure I knew
몇시간동안 만들던거?
you meticulously sourced
and prepped for hours?
당연하지 나는 꼼꼼하게
That's because
I meticulously sourced it
확인하는 남자니까
and prepped it for hours.
너는 형사잖아.
Dude, you're a detective.
적어도 나한테 거짓말을 한다면
If you're gonna lie to me,
증거를 숨겨야하잖아
at least hide
the evidence better.
무슨소리하는거야
I don't know what
you're talking about.
"엄마가 싸주는 가이도 푸드"
쓰레기통에 있더라?
Mamma Guido's Fast Food wrappers
in the trash?
하! 내 쓰레기통을 뒤졌구만!
Ha! You dug through my trash.
나는 그냥 껌을 버렸을 뿐이야
I was throwing away gum.
사생활을 침해했어
You invaded my personal space.
나의 믿음을 배신했고
You-you betrayed my trust.
아마도 니가 심어놓은 걸지도 모르지
어떻게 내게..
You probably planted it there.
How dare you!
인정하는 것도 없고, 부인하지도 않고
그리고 역으로 화내고
Admit nothing, deny everything
and make counter-accusations.
시도는 좋았어. 하지만
우린 같은 심문자 등급을 가졌잖아.
Nice try. We went to the same
interrogation classes.
그래서 고소할거야?
Gonna cost me, isn't it?
아마도, 그리고 절대로 언제
닥칠지 알지못하겠지
Mm-hmm, and you'll never
see it coming.
왠지 오늘은 내동료 요원이
늦잠자는거 같아
Seems like our fellow agents
decided to sleep in today.
지금이 몇시지?
Oh, what time is it?
적어도 한시간 전엔 왔어야되
About an hour after
they should have been here.
캘런선배한테 전화해볼게
Wow.
I'll call Callen.
나는 샘선배한테
I'll call Sam.
음성메시지로 넘어가는데
Gone straight to voice mail.
나도
Sam's, too.
에릭이랑 넬한테가서
확인해보자
Let's check with
Eric and Nell.
조셉 아밥이라는중요할지도
모르는 증인을 만나는일이라
I don't have to stress
that Abaq could be
위험하진 않을겁니다.
the most important cooperating
witness that we've encountered.
2주 전까지
Given that we weren't aware
of an ISIS cell in Los Angeles
LA에 ISIS가 있다는 사실을
우린 알지못했네.
until two weeks ago,
ISIS때문이라도 어떤 위험이
있을지 모르는 일이고
your stressing the point
is indeed redundant,
오웬
Owen.
정보제공자에 대한 어떤
정보라도 있나?
Do you have any further
information on this witness?
우리가 아는건 조셉 아밥은
All we know about
Joseph Abaq is
시리아계 미국인 2세대란 겁니다.
he's second-generation
Syrian-American.
여기서 태어났지만
기록은 없습니다.
Born here, no record.
고등학교 졸업이후
최저임금직장에서 일하고있습니다.
Held minimum-wage jobs
since high school.
그럼 평범한것 말고
주목할만한게 있나?
So, nothing out of the ordinary?
지금까진 없었지만
오마르 휴바락과 연락한적 있습니다.
Not until he started
communicating with Omar Hubarak,
의심가는 통화몇번이 발견됬어요.
the suspected
head of the cell.
이남자는 중요한 인물이에요.
He's been a key player
자하드를 비롯한
중동운동을 주도했습니다.
in various Middle East
Jihadist movements
15년 전부터요.
for the last 15 years.
정보에 따르면 6개월전에
입국한걸로 나와요.
They think he entered the
country about six months ago.
인터넷으로 몇번 대화를 했고
전화도 한걸로 나옵니다.
Web chatter alluded
to his forming a cell.
지금 까지 몰랐던것은
Just didn't know
where until
교통카메라에 그가 찍혔었어요.
a traffic cam caught him on PCH.
아밥과 함께
With Mr. Abaq.
팀이 준비됬나요?
Is the team prepped?
캘런군과 해나군이 아밥과
만나기로했다네.
Mr. Callen and Mr. Hanna will be
backup when you meet with Abaq
오늘 오후에 말일세
this afternoon.
켄지 딕스는 준비됬습니까?
What about Kensi and Deeks?
블라이양은 종업원으로ㅡ
딕스군은 요리사로 잠입하기로했네
Ms. Blye as a waitress,
Mr. Deeks in the kitchen.
딕스가 요리를 한다고요?
Deeks is cooking?
그냥 멕시코 음식점일세
오웬
Well, it's a Mexican
restaurant, Owen.
프랑스 음식점이 아니라
It's not, uh,
the French Laundry.
게다가 자네는 그렇게 생각치 않겠지만
딕스군은 충분한 신용을 가지고있네.
Besides, I don't think you give
Mr. Deeks enough credit.
딕스가만든 스웨덴식 나쵸와
His Swedish nachos
휴일파티는 크게 성공했지
were the hit
of the holiday party.
저는 그파티에 초대받지 못한거 같은데요.
I didn't get my invitation.
좋은일은 아니겠지.
I take it this isn't good.
캘런과 샘이 아직 출근을 안했어요.
Callen and and Sam haven't
shown up for work yet.
전화해도 음성메일로 넘어가고요
Their, uh, cells are
going straight to voicemail,
음성을 남겨도 반응이 없어요.
and they're not
responding to texts.
샘과 캘런은 실종된 NSA분석관을
They were following
up on a tip
쫒다가 실종된거 같습니다.
about a possible
missing NSA analyst.
심각한것은 GPS추적기가
Worst of all,
their GPS trackers
먹통이에요. 찾을수없어요.
have been shut off.
괜찮아?
You okay?
"괜찮다"는 니가 어떻게 정의
하느냐에 달라지지
It depends
on your definition of "okay."
여기가 어디야?
Where are we?
보기엔 기계실같은데
Looks like a machinery
room or something.
섬광탄과 연막탄
A flashbang,
some smoke grenade.
안정제에 제압당해 정신을 잃었어.
And tranquilizer darts
to knock us out.
강철문이야
Solid steel.
보기엔 강철로 창문을
막아버린거 같아
Looks like they welded
metal plates over the windows.
누가우리를 여기에 가뒀는지는 몰라도
Whoever put us in here went
through a lot of trouble
못나가게 하려는 노력은 잘해놨네
to make sure we didn't get out.
신선한 공기가 느껴져
Fresh air.
적어도 우리가 살아있길원하네
At least they're trying
to keep us alive.
이곳에 뭔갈 집어넣을때 까지는
Until they start
pumping something else in here.
누구든지 캘런과 샘과 마지막으로
말했던 사람있나?
When was the last time
anyone spoke with them?
저기,
Well,
저희가 어제 퇴근하면서 대화를했었어요.
we were the last ones
to leave yesterday.
네
Yeah.
샘이 캐런과 집에가는동안
Um, Sam said he
was headed home
아프가니스탄의 유명한 스포츠인
부즈카시에 대한
to watch a documentary
about Buzkashi,
다큐멘터리를 본걸 얘기했구요.
the national sport
of Afghanistan.
얘기를 듣던 캘런이 빈정대는
반응을 보였고
At which point Callen
made a snarky comment
아는체를 조금더 하다가
그를 생일 파티에 데려갔어요.
about knowing what to
get him for his birthday.
그러니까, 평범한 얘기뿐이군?
So, nothing unusual.
예. 평범한것들 뿐이었지만
이대화에 껴든다면
No, nothing, uh, revelatory
about the conversation.
그러니까 둘이 대화했던 것에
제입장은
I mean, about
the situation, that is.
저는 약간 놀라면서 얘기를 들었거든요.
For me, myself,
I was amazed to learn
부즈카시는 사실 거의
아니 정확히 폴로랑 비슷해요
that Buzkashi is actually
almost exactly like polo,
선수가 공을
except for,
instead of a ball,
끌어서 골을 하는것이 폴로라면
the players drag
부즈카시는 죽은 염소를 베는것이
점수로 인정되는것 빼고 다 똑같아요.
the decapitated corpse of a goat
across the goal line to score.
제말은, 죄송해요.
I mean, I'm sorry.
제가 말한 제입장이라던가
이런거는 전부..
I didn't mean to make light
of the situation-- it's just,
조금 걱정되요
I'm a little worried.
그래서 실종된 NAS분석가와
관련해서
So, what do we know
about the NSA tip
우리가 아는게 뭐야?
that they were following up on?
그게좀 애매해요.
Well, it's pretty vague.
저희는 익명의 전화를 받았구요
We received
an anonymous phone call
이른 아침에 NSA 분석가가
early this morning
regarding the possible
실종됬다고 전했습니다.
disappearance
of an analyst.
샘과 캘런이 만났었어야 하는
They were supposed to meet
익명의 제보자 위치는 여기에요.
the anonymous tipster here
비포장 도로위인
Bouquet Canyon in Santa Clarita.
at a dirt road off
마지막으로 GPS신호 있던곳은
저기고요.
Which is where the last
readable GPS signal puts them.
익명의 전화를 추적해봤어?
Where did the anonymous
phone call come from?
선불폰이에요.
A burn phone.
추측하건데 우린 가진게 거의 없어서
Yeah, I'm guessing
we don't have
많은 감시카메라혹은
마을전체를 살펴봐야되네 혹은 둘다거나
a lot of video support out there
in Hooterville, either.
접선장소는 적어도 3마일 안으로는
방범용,교통카메라가 전혀없는 지역이야
Nearest security or traffic cams
are at least three miles out.
딕스군과 블라이양은
여행을 떠날준비를 해야겠네
Mr. Deeks, Ms. Blye,
I think you know your brief.
Yeah.
니가 생각하기엔 진짜로
NSA분석가가 사라졌을꺼같아?
You think there really was
a missing NSA analyst,
아니면 그냥 미끼일까?
or it was just a lure?
모르겠어
I have no idea.
최근에 누구 화나게 했나
You piss anyone off recently?
그냥 미쉘
Just Michelle.
오 그래? 그래서 우리가
Oh, yeah?
What was it this time--
쓰레기 더미위에 있는건가
the garbage or the dishes?
상관없어
It doesn't matter.
미쉘이 화나도 우릴
납치할거라는 생각은안해
I don't think
she's the one who kidnapped us.
그건 잘모르겠어 샘
I don't know
about that, Sam.
너도 니입으로 말했잔아
그녀는 가끔 과잉반응을 할때가 있다고
You said yourself, she's
been known overreact once in a while.
개소리 다 끝났어?
You finished being ridiculous?
아마도
I could be.
그럼 이거 한번 봐바
Take a look at this.
숨겨진 출입구군
Access panel.
나사가 새거야
Nice flat heads, look new.
Yeah.
우린 나사를 풀수있는
철조각이 필요해
We need something metal
with a flat edge,
드라이버나
to use as a screwdriver.
공구가방
Tool bag.
그나마 좋은것은 우리중에
저 틈으로 손이들어가는 사람이 있네
It's a good thing one of us
isn't into pumping iron.
또다른 좋은것은
It's a good thing
one of us
저 기계를 끌수있는 사람이 있다는거지
is into pumping iron.
잡았어?
Got it?
잡았어
Now I do.
여기
Here.
줘바
Give me that...
보기엔 터널같은 거군
Looks like a tunnel
of some sort.
터널?
Tunnel?
Yeah.
아마도 재료를 변환해서
It was probably used
to transport material in
밖으로 내보내는 길같은데
from the outside.
괜찬아?
You all right?
말하지말고 그냥 가
Let's just
keep moving.
상황이 스티브 맥퀸의 영화를
떠올리게하네
This kind of reminds me
of that Steve McQueen movie,
위대한 탈출
The Great Escape.
그런걸 말하는게 내기분을 좋게하는거 같아?
Is that your idea of
making me feel better?
그냥 말하는거지
끝에가면 우린 다..
I'm just saying,
in the end, they all m...
자유를 얻게 될거야
they all made it
to freedom.
지하동굴에서 공황발작을
일으킨다는
Not before Charles Bronson
had a panic attack
영화를 한번도 본적이 없구나
when the tunnel caved in.
그 부분은 잊어 그냥
Let's forget that part.
주제를 바꾸든가 하자
Let's just change the subject.
All right.
너는 왜 니 생일파티를 원치
않는거야?
Why don't you tell me what
you want for your birthday, huh?
그냥 닥치고 나가자고
/그건 할수있어
To get the hell out of this tunnel.
All right. We can do that.
이제부턴 그냥 말을 하지말자
How 'bout we just
not talk. At all.
그것도 할수있을거야
We can do that, too. Okay.
나무벽이네
Piece of wood.
보기엔 박혀있는거 같아
Looks like that's
just wedged in there.
안쪽에서 나사로 잠궈졌어
Looks like it's screwed
into the wall from the inside.
좋네
So that's good.
드라이버줘
Yeah. Give me the screwdriver.
빨리
Come on.
드라이버 안 가져와도돼
You didn't bring the screwdriver.
How was I supposed to know
우리가 필요한건 드라이버를
누가 가져오느냐야
we were gonna need
the screwdriver again?
이런걸 '앞서생각하기'
라고해 우리가 하는거지
It's called thinking ahead.
That's what we do.
니가 드라이버를 가져왔어야지
You could've brought
the screwdriver.
지금은 니가 뒤에있잔아
You had it last.
혹시 드라이버를 가지고 와줄래?
Would you like to go get
the screwdriver?
아니.
그럼 내가 가져왔으면 좋겠어?
No.
Would you like me to get it?
ㅇㅇ
Yes.
지금 화났어?
약간
Are you irritated?
A little.
그냥 개같은 드라이버좀
빨리가져왔으면 좋겠어
But mostly I want you to just
get the damn screwdriver.
내가 가져온다
I'm gonna get the screwdriver.
클리어
Clear.
Yeah.
타이어 자국이야
Fresh tire tracks.
만남사람이 하나이상이었던듯
Looks like the only ones around.
자국이 큰걸로 봐서
They look big.
아마도 픽업트럭이나 SUV..
Maybe a pickup truck, SUV...
싸움 흔적은 없어보이고
There's no signs
of a struggle.
차는 버려졌어
Car wasn't tossed.
또한 거칠고 황량한 곳이야
It's also a big wide open space.
운이없다면 힘들겠어
No chance for surprises.
어쩌면 우리가 대화하는게
시간낭비일거야
So maybe we're talking
about numbers.
계속찾아볼께
I'll keep looking.
Yeah.
헤이 켄지
Hey, Kens.
현장에 있던 타이어 자국을
지금 너한테 보낼게
Hey, Nell, I just sent you
a photo of tire tracks.
어쩌면 모델명을 알수있을거야
See if you can narrow down
the make and model.
바로 시작할께요
On it.
고마워
켄질리나
Thank you.
Kensilina.
왜
Yes.
좋은 소식과 나쁜소식이 있어
I got some good news
and some bad news.
연막탄
Smoke grenade.
계속 찾아봐
Let's keep searching.
여기
Hey.
그게뭐야
What's that?
진정제 다트
I got a tranquilizer dart.
그리고 섬광탄
And a flashbang fuse.
All right.
섬광탄,연막탄,진정제
Flashbang, smoke, ketamine.
그래서 못찾는거야
That's how they took 'em out.
그냥 제압당한거야
So they just wanted 'em
incapacitated.
"그냥"?
"Just"?
그게 더 낫지 핏자국을 찾는거보단
It's better
than finding bloodstains.
증거로 섬광탄을 찾았다네
There was evidence
of a flashbang
그리고 진정제 다트와 함께
and a ketamine dart
샘과 캘런의 마지막 위치에서 말일세
at Sam and Callen's
last location.
그장소에 목격자는 없습니까?
Any chance someone saw something?
The area
고립된 지역이라네
is isolated.
누가 무슨이유로 그곳을
선택했든
Which I'm sure
is why it was chosen
약속장소로 정했네
as the meeting point.
또한 보기힘든 우연의 일치고요.
It's also one hell
of a coincidence
중대한 작전이있는날
on the day of a crucial op
우리의 첫번째 ISIS 정보원말이에요.
기억하시죠?
with our first ISIS informant,
you know?
타이밍의 대해선 동의하나
아직은 섯부르게 생각할수없네
I agree. The timing raises
at least a yellow flag.
NSA에 배신자가 있을수도있지만
그들의 분석가가 사라졌다는것은 확실한것 같아
I've reached out to NSA
regarding their missing analyst.
자하디스트 웹 사이트에
See if they've heard any chatter
on the Jihadist Web sites
휴바락과 아랍이 떳습니다.
about Hubarak or Abaq.
그들보다 빠르게 움직이게
오웬
Ahead of you, Owen.
당신은 항상빠르지요,
헨리에타
You always are, Henrietta.
당신이 당신팀에 대해
걱정하는건 잘압니다
Listen, I'm as concerned
about them as you are.
하지만 그들보다 당장은
작전이 우선순위입니다.
But this meeting with Abaq
must go on as planned.
이해했네
Understood.
밖으로 나왔어
And we're out.
내가 뭐라고 말했냐
What'd I tell you?
위대한 탈출.이라고
Just like The Great Escape.
아직도 그영화 안봤냐
Did you even
watch that movie?
탈출하던중에 터널에서
다 총맞아 죽는데
Half of the guys got shot after
they got out of the tunnel.
그래도 우린 해냈잔아
Well, the other half
made it.
우린 운좋은쪽인거 같아
Guess I'm a bright-side
kind of guy.
카메라가 하나도 없어
Don't see any
security cams.
다른곳에 있을수도있어
There weren't any
inside either.
우리가 어딨는거야?
Where are we?
숨겨진 지역이던가..
It's the wrong topography
to be...
Angeles Crest 나 La Canada.
Angeles Crest or La Ca챰ada.
확실히
Central Los Angeles은 아냐
Definitely not
Central Los Angeles.
저 산중턱에 집이 있어야하는데
There'd be houses on those hills.
Deep
Topanga안쪽인가? Malibu일지도?
in Topanga? Malibu, maybe?
Santa Clarita Valley?
도대체 이일의 배후는
뭐하는 인간일까 허?
So who the hell's
behind this, huh?
원하는게 뭐야?
What do they want?
어쩌면 간단한 복수일지도 모르지
우리가 누군갈 열받게 했을수도
Could be as simple as payback
from someone we busted.
그거보다는 더 큰일인거같아
It feels bigger than that.
우리를 어디로 데려온걸까
The way they took us out.
계획된 사형일지도
Well planned, well executed.
우리가 있던방은 원래 저상태
였을까
That room they
kept us in.
아닐꺼야 많은 돈과 시간을
투자했어
Spent a lot
of time and money.
그리고 저것도있네
And then there's this.
저건 한 2미터 정도하나?
What is that,
eight feet high?
가시 철책이 아닌데
No barbed wire.
너무 쉬운데
It's almost too easy.
아마도 이것때문이겠지
Because it is.
두번째 작전?
Plan B?
멈춰!
Stop!
한발자국만 더 가면
죽을껍니다.
One more step
and you're a dead man.
당신들 다리가 함정 줄을
건드렸어요
Your leg is brushing up
against a fishing line.
봤어요?
You see it?
함정이에요.
It's
a trip wire.
그가맞아 G, 움직이지마
He's right, G.
Don't move.
안움직일께
Not moving.
저뒤에서 봤어요
I saw one like it
back there.
이 함정은 고정된 스프링이
거기에 부착되있어요.
It's attached to a spring-loaded
device that releases a board
함정이 발동이되면 가슴높이의
위치에 발사체가 날라올거에요.
embedded with nails in it,
striking chest high.
심장쪽이야
Into the heart.
Okay.
이게 내 계획이야
Here's what we're gonna do.
듣고있어
I'm all ears.
셋을 셀게
On the count
of three,
니가 할수있는한 빠르게
땅으로 엎드려
you're gonna drop to the ground
as fast as you can.
난 충분히 빨라
I can do fast.
준비됬어?
You ready?
하나.. 둘..
One, two...
고마워요
Thanks.
근데 누구시죠?
Who are you?
마틴 사미르 NSA
Martin Samir, NSA.
Whoa!
움직이지마!
Don't move.
움직이지마세요.
댁들은 누구세요?
Who are you guys?
NCIS 해나 , 캘런이에요.
Agents Hanna and Callen, NCIS.
인사한마디 건내기어렵네요.
It's a hell of a way
to say hello.
기관에서 분석가로 10년이면
같은편을 알아보기 마련이죠
Insurgent analyst for ten years.
You know what to look for.
고마워요
Thank you.
별거아니에요
No problem.
오늘아침에 정보가 있었는데
We got a tip this morning
실종된 NSA요원에 대해서였어요.
about a missing NSA analyst.
아마도 저를 말하는거같네요.
Guess that's me.
하지만 장소로 갔더니 함정이었고
우리도 납치됬습니다.
It was a setup to kidnap us.
아침에 사무실근처에서
괴한들에게 납치당했어요.
They grabbed me near the office
this morning.
스타벅스에서 나오던 길이었어요.
Went out for a Starbucks.
납치당할때 목격자나
교통카메라나 아무거나 있었나요?
Any surveillance?
Traffic cams? Anything?
없을거에요. 골목길에서 당했으니까요.
I doubt it.
It was a side street.
누군가 절 미행했을거에요.
They must have been tailing me.
NSA사무실을 나왔을때
When you left NSA,
출구와 차고는 각각 어느
방향에 있었습니까?
where'd you exit
the garage from?
주 정문은 월셔가에 있고요
The main exit on Wilshire,
주차장은 웨스턴방향이요.
drove towards Western.
교통카메라는 월셔쪽에
많이있어
Traffic cams on Wilshire
probably picked 'em up.
차고있는 수갑은 뭐에요?
What's with the cuffs?
정신차려보니 쇠파이프에
메져있던데요.
I-I woke up out here,
cuffed to a metal pipe.
시간좀 걸려서 파이프를 뺐어요.
Took a while,
but I managed to get free.
당신들은?
You guys?
잠겨진방에서요. 나가는길을 찾았어요.
Locked room. Found a way out.
그들은 우리가 이렇게 얘기중인걸
원치않을꺼에요
They probably didn't want us
talking to each other.
"그들"이 누군지 아는거 있어요?
You have any idea
who "they" are?
내가 깨어난후에 잠담하는걸
들었어요.
I heard a little chatter
before I passed out.
아마도 ISIS일겁니다.
Pretty sure it's ISIS.
오마르 휴바락?
Omar Hubarak?
그리고 조셉아밥
And Joseph Abaq.
NSA에서 아밥에 대해 아는게 있어요?
What do you people know
about Abaq?
우린 지난달에 그를 추적을 시도했어요.
We've been trying to track him
for the past few months.
우리들끼리 말하자면
그는 관련되있는거같아요.
As far as we can tell,
he's an associate
여기 :LA에서 휴바락과 몇번
통화를했어요.
of the cell
that Hubarak leads, here in L.A.
들리는 소문에의하면 그는 그룹에 반역자이고
그가가진 정보로 거래를 할거라는군요
There's rumors he's a traitor,
feeding Intel to the Feds.
소문?
Rumors?
정확하진 않아요
Unsubstantiated.
우리도 믿지않고요.
We don't believe it.
휴바락이 뭔가 큰 계획을 가진거
같아요.
We think Hubarak has
something big planned,
아밥이관련된 어떤
발표를 할거라 생각해요.
to make a statement,
and it involves Abaq.
하지만 우린 그와관련된
어떤것도 확인할수없었어요.
But we're not
sure what it is.
다른 개판이벌어졌군, G
Another fine mess, G.
전기 울타리를 멈출수있는곳
을 찾아봐야되요.
Let's see if we can find a break
in the fence somewhere.
흠 타이어 자국은 알기어렵네요.
Well...
the tires are a no-brainer.
저 타이어를 쓰는 차는 몇개의
푸드트럭이 있고요
They're on several Ford trucks
1990년 부터 생산됬고
2006년에 단종됬어요.
from 1990 to 2006.
그럼 얼마나 많은 트럭을 살펴봐야되?
And how many trucks
is that total?
오, 그냥
몇천개정도요.
Oh, just
a few thousand
LA지역만 봐서요.
/환장하겠네
in the L.A. area alone.
Great.
다른쪽을 보자면,
On the better news side,
딕스가 발견한 섬광탄과
연막탄이
your flashbang
and smoke grenade
무기와 몇몇 폭발물과 장비들을
포함한 박스에 있던거래
were part of a cache of
weapons and equipment
국가방위군 물건이고
from a National Guard
저번달이 배송중이던 물건들이였고
차량을 탈취당했답니다.
transport truck
hijacked last month.
꽤 대담한데
/그리고 성공적이야
That's a bold move.
It's a big payoff.
LAPD는 두명의 용의자를 잡았어요.
아르메니안을 잡아서 구금중이야.
LAPD has two suspects
from Armenian Power in custody.
ATF에서 잠재적 무기 구매자 몇명의
목록을 확보했어요.
ATF narrowed the list
of potential buyers.
첫번째로 길거리 무기상인
Uh, number one candidate
is a low-level arms dealer,
오스카 윌럿
one Oscar Willits.
윌럿이 중개인인건 알았어
Okay, so Willits
is the middleman.
그는 '합법적이고 무결하고
오스카 윌럿의 무제한
He's legitimately incorporated
as Oscar Willits Limited,
사업 기획 컨설턴팅 회사'
라네요.
a business management
consulting firm.
장난치는거지?
그게 위장회사 이름이야?
Oh, you're kidding me--
that's his cover?
네
Yep.
이게 그의 사무실
And that's his office.
와우, 무제한에
대해
Wow. That's
the very definition
정의하기 쉽겠는데
of "limited."
Santa Clarita,에 그의 사무실이 있어요
3마일 떨어진곳이
And it's in Santa Clarita,
three miles from where
캘런과 샘이 납치당한곳이에요.
Callen and Sam were taken.
그럼 누가 그의 고객일까
So who's
his clients,
방울뱀과 모든지역의
허니부부?
rattlesnakes and the whole cast
of Honey Boo Boo?
NSA에서 공식정으로 분석가가
사라진거에대해 인정했다네
NSA has just confirmed
they have a missing analyst.
마틴 사미르
Martin Samir.
블라이양, 딕스군
Ms. Blye, Mr. Deeks,
기획사에 한번 제안하는게
좋을것같네
I suggest you go and get
some management advice,
가능한 빨리
ASAP.
다녀오겠습니다.
Never hurts.
아밥은 3시에 부국장과
만나기로했어
Abaq is meeting with our
assistant director at 3:00.
식당이름은 루시 엘 아도비
Lucy's El Adobe.
아마 함정일거에요.
It's got to be a setup.
그를 죽이고 공개적으로
쿠테타를 하지않을까요
Killing him would make
for a public relations coup.
빨리 탈출해서 그레인저와
만나야되
We need to find a way
to get in touch with Granger.
잠겼는데
It's locked.
여기야
Over there.
우리가 오는걸 못봤어
Well, no way
he doesn't see us coming.
Mm.
내차를 세차하고싶다
I just got my
car washed.
더러운 비포장도로를
넘어왔으니까
Now I'm gonna have
to barrel it across a dirt road and...
한다는 소리가 그거야?
차를 세차한다고?
This is your clever way of saying that
I'll be the one heading him off on foot?
내생각엔 '엄마가 싸주는 가이도'가
최고인듯
I think Mama Guido said it best.
허,투셰이
Huh. Touch챕.
안녕하세요 월렛씨
/뭘 원하는거요?
Hey, Mr. Willits.
What do you want?
내 사업에대해 조언을
좀 얻고싶어 왔어요
I just came to get some advice
about my business.
예약 먼저 해야는데요.
You'll have to make
an appointment.
예약이요? 그래도 차몰고 여기까지 왔는데
Make an appointment?
I just drove all the way out here.
얘기하는것도 안되요?
길지않을겁니다
We can't talk now?
It's not gonna take that long.
가시오
Go away.
여기 잠깐들어봐요.
나는 주로 오크라를 수출합니다.
Here's the deal--
I do import-export, mostly okra,
하지만 더욱 고급의 채소를
들어오려고 노력하죠
but I'm trying to get into
more high-end vegetables,
귤도 괜찮구요.
아니면 깻잎도
like kumquats
and fiddleheads.
그러지마.. 연방요원이다!
Don't... Federal agents!
멈춰!!
Freeze!
아..안돼 물안에 안들어갈꺼야
No, n-not in
the water.
존나 차가워보이는데..
That looks incredibly cold.
아 존나 추워.. 존나추워!!
Aah! Oh, God, that's cold!
뭐하는거야?
What are you doing?
어디가냐!!
Where are you going?
니계획은 대채뭐야
What-what is your plan here,
내가 미끄러져서 기절하길
바라는거야?
that I'm gonna slip
and knock myself unconscious?
켄지 쏴버려!
Kensi, shoot him.
윌렛!!
Willits!
포기해
Get up.
안한다고?
/연방요원이다!
- Done?
- Federal agents.
그만 포기해 월렛
Stop struggling, Willits.
다끝났어
It's over, man.
그냥 말하는건데
Just for the record...
너 엄마가 싸주는 가이도
접시까지 핥아 먹엇잔아
you licked that Mama
Guido plate clean.
우린 당신에 협력하겠습니다.
We'll give you
our full cooperation
일도 함께하며 요원들도
같을수 있도록
so we can work together
and find our people.
고맙습니다.
Thank you.
찾은게 있으세요?
You find anything?
사미르씨는 아예 출근하지 않았다는군
Mr. Samir never showed up
for work this morning.
NSA에서 그의 아파트가
어지러진 채로 발견했다네
An NSA team swept
his apartment
그리고 우리 요원들을 찾기위해
노력하고 있네
and found signs
of a struggle.
다음은 어디로가지?
So what's
our next move?
같은질문을 너한테 하고싶었느데
That was gonna be
my question to you.
잠깐 괜찬다면 소변좀
If you guys don't mind,
uh, nature calls.
♪ ♪
솵 솵
사미르
Samir!
잠깐! 집중중이에요.
Yeah. I'm a little
preoccupied here.
잠깐 파트너와 얘기해 봤는데
Talked it over
with my partner.
가장좋은 계획은
We think the best plan
전력을 차단시키는거에요
is to break back
into the building,
차단기를 찾아서 전기를 끈고
울타리를 넘는게 좋을거같습니다.
find ourselves a way
to cut the power to the fence.
그럽시다
All right.
준비됬습니까?
Ready to roll?
가고있어요
I'm coming, I'm coming.
이미 말했잔아요
I already told you,
나는 사업기획 컨설털트 일뿐이라고
I'm a business management
consultant.
흠 그게 사실이면
Hmm. Well,
putting aside the fact
당신의 사무실은 숲속에있는데
you're operating your business
out in Green Acres,
그렇담 잠재적인 고객들은 숲친구들인가봐요
not a lot of consultants
run away from potential clients.
예를들면 호수같은거요
Especially
through a lake.
이방인을 조심해서 나쁠거 없잖아요
I'm always wary of strangers.
이건 내가 가지고있는 많은 지혜중하나고
It's one of the many
pearls or wisdom
나는 많은 사람들을 피해 사업하는게 좋아요.
I like to pass on to the people
I do business with.
특별하게 몇개를 꼽자면 무기나
폭발물을 파는게 사업이신가봐요?
Oh, especially the ones that
you sell stolen explosives and weapons to.
그건 진실이아니에요
That's not true.
레알?
Isn't it?
저기요 내가 매일 컨설턴트일을
해주진않아요
Look, I know I don't look
like your everyday consultant.
그게 내 독특한 방식이고요
/뭐가 당신을 독특하게 만들어주냐면
- That's what makes me unique.
- No, no, what makes you unique,
오스카 AR-15들과 5000발의 총알과
Oscar, is the, uh, dozen AR-15s,
5,000 rounds of ammo,
몇개의 도난당한 섬광탄들
and another dozen
stolen flashbang grenades
그게 우리가 찾을 당신기업본부일텐데요
that were found in a shed next
to your corporate headquarters.
이건 우연이 아니라니까요
Not a lot of that
happening at AIG.
당신이 판 폭발물은 두명의
연방요원을 납치하는데 쓰였어요.
Explosives that were used in
the abduction of two Federal agents.
나는 그것들이 왜 거깃는지
전혀모르겠네요
I have no idea
how those got there.
Hm. You know what,
despite the fact that
우리의 파트너들은 심각한
문제에 빠졌어요 당신때문에
our partners could be
in serious trouble because of you,
이건... 새해네요
it is... it is a new year.
무슨소린지 알죠?
Know what I mean?
And I am a...
누구든지 새출발할수있는
자격이있어요.
firm believer that everyone
deserves a fresh start.
종종 쟤는 저러는걸 좋아해요
He gets like this
sometimes.
내가 약간 알고있는게 있는데
I have an inkling
그냥 보내줄께요
just to let you go.
무슨소린줄 아시져?
Know what I mean?
귀찬은 30년 감옥행 피하고
좋잔아요?
Just avoid that pesky
30 years in prison.
할수있어요?
You do?
그리고 그냥 나무밖에 없는 구석에
당신을 놓고가는거지
Yeah. Drop you off at the corner
of Florence and Inglewood...
엄청난 약물증세가 나타날꺼고
쓰러졌다 일어났다를 반복할때
while a major drug bust is
going down, pat you on the back
등을 두드리며 "도와줘서 고마웠어!"
한마디하고 가버리는거야
and say, "Thanks for all your help."
That should be enough
주변 동네사람들의 주목을 받게 되겠지만
to get the attention of
the local Neighborhood Watch,
어떻게 생각해
don't you think?
하지만 우린 정보제공자를위해 200달러를
줘야하잔아
Well, we can't forget
the $200 informant fee
그리고 천천히 돈을세는거야
Right.
that we would count out slowly
사람들이 보는앞에서
in front of the MS-13
youth league.
뭐 그래도
That's if
you're a fan
새출발을 할수있잖아?
of fresh starts.
준비됐어 오스카?
Are you, Oscar?
하지만 그게 아니라면 너는 아마도
But if not, you
should probably
어딘가에서 새시작을 하게될꺼야
go ahead and drop
one of those little, uh...
진주와 지혜로 너를 도울지
아님 우리에 말을해
pearls of wisdom on us
and let us know who it is
훔친 섬광탄을 누구에게 팔았는지
you sold those stolen
flashbang grenades to.
알게되서 반가웠어.
That would work, too.
창문으로 우리가 다가오는걸
볼수있을거야
Check out the windows on
the front half of the building.
건물안에 있다면 어디든지
숨어있을거야
It doesn't look like
they're covered with anything.
방이 여러개 있을거에요.
Must be a
separate room.
그말이 말을거야
That's probably where
our guys set up shop.
그리고 아직도 저기에 있겠지
They could still be in there.
무장한상태일게 뻔해요.
If they are,
they're gonna be armed.
할수있겠어요?
You up for this?
내가 분석가일지는 몰라도
내 앞가림은 내가 합니다
I may be an analyst,
but I can handle myself.
우리는 작은 건물뒤로 엄페할겁니다.
We use that smaller building
as cover.
어쩌면 우리가 오늘걸 볼수도
있어요.
Make it harder for them
to see us coming.
가까이가서 어디가 최선의길인지
확인해야되
We get closer,
we'll decide the best way in.
우리가 리드할께요.
We'll take the lead on this.
떨어지지마세요.
You stick close.
알았어요.
Got it.
뭐라도 찾았어?
Anything?
오스카 윌렛이 정보를 알려주면서
I think we found the truck
that matches the description
설명해준 용의자의 트럭을 찾은거같아.
that Oscar Willits
gave you.
철제 지붕 틀,
나무 선반, 범퍼 가드
Dually crew cab,
wood rack, brush guard,
차 옆구리에 하얀색 스크레치
자국
white paint scrapes on
the right front fender.
확대좀 해줘
Zoom in on the cab.
Yeah.
동승자 쪽으로 확대를 더해봐
Can you get closer to the passenger?
Mm-hmm.
좀더 깨끗하게 해줄래?
Can you clean that up?
그래
Sure.
봐바
There it is.
도난된 무기를 찾았어
언제 어디서 찍힌사진이야?
- Tranq gun.
- When and where?
캘런과 샘이
Half an hour
before Callen and Sam
익명의 정보제공자를 만나는
were supposed
to meet their tip guy,
곳에서 5마일 떨어진 곳이야
만나기 30분전이고
five miles from the meeting spot.
We already called it in
고속도로 순찰대에 경보를 내렸어요
to the Highway Patrol.
Now we're going through
이부근의 가장 최근 교통카메라
traffic-cam footage
to see if we can
를 볼수가 있을거에요.
find a more
recent hit.
찾았어
Oh. Got it.
이건 45분전에 찍힌거야 장소는 올드타팡가
잘했어
- This is 45 minutes ago, off Old Topanga.
- Nice.
완벽해 출동하자
Perfect. Let's go.
어디가는건가?
에릭이
Where are you going?
Eric got a hit
납치범들의 트럭을 찾았어요
하지만 그장소는
on the kidnappers' truck.
We have an op
45분전의 장소이고
맞는 말씀이지만
in 45 minutes.
Yeah, what we have
캘런과 샘을 어서 구해야되요
is Callen and Sam
in trouble.
이미 다른팀이 그들을 쫒고 있다네
I'll assign another team
to the truck lead.
다른 팀..
최대한 존경을 담아 말씀드리는데..
Another tea...
No, with all due respect, sir...
내말 듣게나
Listen to me.
이건 존경이 필요치않는 일이야
This has nothing to do
with respect.
캘런과 샘에게 생각하는
마음은 잘알아
I know what you're feeling
about Callen and Sam.
믿거나 말거나 나도 자네들 마음과
다르지 않고
Whether you want to believe it
or not, I feel the same way.
하지만 이기회는
But this is a chance
ISIS그룹내의
to take down the only known
익명의 제보자를 찾는
ISIS cell in the country,
유일한 기회가 될껄세
and you're prepped for the op.
자네들이 필요해
I need you.
♪ ♪
솵 솵
재빠르게 부수고 들어가야되
We need to break it
fast and get in.
제가 아까 말했죠.
우리가 리드합니다.
I told you,
we'll take point on this.
너무 오래있어요
He's been in there
too long.
아무것도 없어
All clear.
전화기를 찾아야되
We've got to find those phones.
차단기를 찾았어
Circuit breaker.
아마 지금쯤 전기울타리의
전력이 나갔을거야
That should cut the power
to the fence.
전화기를 찾아
Find the phones.
누구세요?
Who are you?
마틴 사미르 NSA
Martin Samir, NSA.
♪ ♪
솵 솵
괜찮으세요?
Everything okay?
니가 만든 음식 맛없어
Your cook sucks.
알아요
Noted.
요리사님
Oh, chef.
종업원씨
Oh, waitress.
그마나 손님이 세명뿐이라 다행이야
Good thing there's only
three other customers in here.
Mm.
분명한건 이정도는 보통일거란말야
Apparently with
very low standards.
내가 뭐하는지 알고있어?
You know what I'm going to do?
널위해서 집에서 만든
알파벳 수프를 만들어 줄깨
I'm going make you
some homemade alphabet soup
그리곤 나의 진짜 음식들을 먹고
단어몇개를 말해주면 좋겠어
so you can eat your words
when you taste my real cooking.
만나서 반갑습니다. 아밥씨
Good to see you, Mr. Abaq.
내려놔
Drop it.
너희들은 이미 늦었어!
You're too late!
나에게 만남장소를 알려줬지
You gave me the meeting place!
우리쪽 사람들에게 보냈지
I sent word to my people!
조만간 너희들의 부국장과
Soon your assistant director
배신자 아밥은 반드시
죽을것이다
and the traitor Abaq
will be dead!
고맙습니다.
Thank you.
시작해도 될까요?
Shall we get started?
정말 이곳은 안전합니까?
You're sure we're safe here?
확신합니다. 이곳에선
당신에대한 어떤위협도 받지않을것이오.
I assure you,
you're in no danger.
10명의 핵심멤버와
The cell has ten core members
몇명의 관련자들에대해 말할께요.
plus associates.
거의 시리아인과 이라크인들이에요.
Almost all Syrian and Iraqi.
대부분 여기서 태어났고요.
Most were born here.
뒷문으로가
Get back!
미안한데 별로 안좋은 뉴스 몇개
알려줄게
Afraid I got some bad news
for you.
우린 널 만난지 10분후에
니가 진짜가 아닌걸 눈치챘어
We knew you weren't real
ten minutes after we met you.
아밥과 만나는 잘못된 장소를
알려줬지
Location I gave you for
the Abaq meeting was wrong.
이미 NCIS에 알렸다
I informed NCIS.
니친구들은 ISIS고
Your buddies from ISIS
그친구들은 무장된 연방요원들에게
포위됬지
are about to get surrounded
by an army of Feds.
연방요원이다!
무기 버려!!
Federal agents!
Drop your weapons!
사격중지!
I said halt!
Clear!
적을 섬멸했다
All clear!
흠 확실히
Well, that's
여섯명의 ISIS멤버들에대한
괜한 걱정이었네요.
six less ISIS cell members
we have to worry about.
나는 진심으로 희망컨데
I just hope that
캘런군과 해나군이 그들자신을 위한
Mr. Callen and Mr. Hanna
have a plan
작전을 가지고있을거라고 말일세
to save themselves.
달아나고있어!
He's running!
받아
Here.
저쪽이야
There he is.
못잡을거 같은데
We're not going to catch him.
쫒아갈 필요가 없잔아
We don't have to.
이름은 자말 네지
His name is Jamal Nezi.
al-Qaeda until 을위해 활동하던
An active jihadist for al-Qaeda
사람이었어요.
until their organization
started to unravel.
새로 결성된 ISIS를 돕기위해 지하디스트인
When ISIS reinvigorated
the jihadist movement,
네지는 새로운 기회란걸 깨달았죠
it provided a new
opportunity for Nezi.
입수된 정보에 의하면 ISIS가 LA에서
활동범위를 넓히자
According to intelligence
reports, the ISIS cell in L.A.
아밥씨는 NCIS와 얘기하려했답니다.
suspected Abaq
of talking to NCIS.
하지만 아밥은 배신한다는것을
들키게되지
But Mr. Abaq was in the
proverbial wind by that point.
그럼 그들은 계획을 세웠어
Okay, so they hatched up a plan.
샘과 캘런을 납치하고 그리고
They kidnap Callen
and Sam and...
NSA요원을 납치후에 감금시켰다고?
make them think an NSA agent
is a fellow captive?
그들은 도망친 아밥에대한 정보를
얻으려고 했겠지
Hoping that they'll give up
Intel freely on Abaq.
하지만 놈들이 몰랐던것은 샘의
지식은 위대해서 NSA건물알고있다는것이지
But they didn't count on Sam's
knowledge of the NSA building.
그렇지!
Yes!
Yeah.
다시 복귀한 둘을 보니 좋군
It's good to have you two back.
저도 좋아요.
Oh, it is good to be back.
오우 말나온김에 내가 깜짝선물을
준비했어
Ooh, speaking of which,
I have a... I have a surprise.
Um...
아까 캘런이 말한게 뭐야
- so what tipped you off?
- Ah.
몇주전에 NSA에 갈일이 있었는데
A couple of weeks ago,
I was at the NSA.
주차장 공사를 하고있더라고
They're doing construction
on the garage.
윌트셔가 방향의 출구는
공사때문에 다음 6주까지 막혔어
The Wilshire exit will be
blocked for the next six weeks.
네지는 윌트셔 방향의 차고에서 나왔다 그랬거든
Nezi told us that he exited
the garage on Wilshire
납치되기 직전에
before he was taken.
샘은 그가 가짜인걸 알았지
Sam knew his cover was bogus.
그래서 창고안으로 들어갔을때
나는
When I broke into the building,
I was able to find
무기랑 전화기를 찾았어 그래서 작전실로
문자를 보낼수있었지
our weapons and my cell phone,
so I texted Ops
우리가 네지에게 말한 장소로
the location
of the phony meeting
스왓팀을 보내라고 말야
that we told Nezi about.
뭐가 생각나냐면
Which reminds me. Uh...
탈출할때 느꼈던 샘의 개판오분전?
"Another fine mess"?
생각해보니 올라올때 암구호같은걸
정할걸 그랬네
Think maybe we could come up
with a watchword
작은 엉덩이? 로웰 앤 하디
a little hipper
than Laurel and Hardy?
로웰 앤 하디 사랑하는데
I love Laurel and Hardy.
덩치큰 남자 똑똑하잖아
The big guy's smart.
샘과 의견이 같아 나도 사랑함
I'm with him--
I love Laurel and Hardy.
집에 안전하게 돌아온거에대해
축하해야겠지!
The perfect thing to celebrate
your safe homecoming,
내 유명한 스위디시 나쵸
my famous Swedish nachos.
자 집어.. 집어먹어봐
Go ahead, dig in.
Just take a...
아..저는....
쫌만 먹어봐
Oh, I'm...
Take a little bit.
They're, uh, they're gluten free.
Oh, not right now.
- Just...
- Thanks, but no.
Um, when, um...
Do you...?
말해야 되지않아요?
So, when we
said that we...
우린 좋아해..
사실은
liked them, we actually
진짜로 우린..
meant... we were...
그냥 상처안받게 얘기하려는거지?
ㅇㅇ..
You were just being polite?
Yeah.
그게 우리가 열심히 일했잔아요.
Well... you worked so hard
그리고 크리스마스였죠
and, you know,
it was Christmas.
미안해요.
그걸 이제야 얘기하는 이유가 뭐야?
Sorry.
And this is coming out now?
그레인저 왔어요?
What's up, Granger?
잠깐만
Wait a minute.
스위디시 나쵸 맞지?
Swedish nachos, right?
맞아요.
나쵸 미트볼?
Yeah.
Nacho meatballs?
맞습니당
Yeah.
저번에 못먹어본게 내심 아쉬웠는데
I missed this
the first time around,
이제야 먹어보는군
I'm not missing it
this time.
내가 지금 시도해보지
드셔보세요
I'm going to try one right now.
Get in there.
Uh...
Mm, mm!
맛이.. 괜찬네?
That's pretty good.
감사합니다. 봤지? 이거 맛있다니까!
Thank you. It's good.
드디어 특별한 미각을 가진분이 나오시네
Finally, someone with a palate.
왜?
What?
아닐세 아무것도
Nothing.
사실은 완벽한 장면이었지
In fact, it makes perfect sense.
Bon appetit.
Bon app챕tit.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man